Software Developer

Career & Life Goal

I'm an independent, self-taught software developer since 2014. Please check out my projects page at https://codingergonomist.github.io/ to see some of my work.

I strive to challenge my skills, never letting a day go by without improvement so I can stand among a team of the best, making highly competitive games that are sought after and profitable.

Education Technical Skills

Simon Fraser University 2008- 2013 Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology Ergonomics Stream Languages: C#, C++, Java, Json

Tools: Unity Engine, Github, Bitbucket, Slack,

MongoDB, Excel and SPSS

Software Experience

Software Developer

Fingerprint Studio Limited, Hong Kong

November 2016 – Present

- Released Triangle 180 on Android and IOS, continuing into a live environment and winning the Taipei Game Show 2017 Audience Choice Award for Indie Games.
- Implemented the puzzle game mode, power ups, increased device compatibility and updated the UI.

Indie Game Developer

2018 - Present

Guilds and Profiteers

- Created a custom server backend using Photon and MongoDB to handle the gameplay logic and enable asynchronous play.
- Developed a backtracking algorithm to calculate character actions.
- Used Unity to create front end for handling inputs while obfuscating other player's lies.

Indie Game Developer

2014 - 2017

Parity of War

- Produced a combat system in the style of Guild Wars 2 with dodging and an extensive skill pool on a peer to peer network.
- Made a RTS role to drop power ups, expand a team's base, customize lane minions and create specialized minions they directly control.

Other Experience

Community Support Worker

December 2017 - Present

Strive Living Society, Burnaby, BC, Canada

- Create activity and community integration plans for persons with varying special needs.
- Teach strategies to help with daily living using specialized communication tools.
- Train new staff and write daily communication reports between staff members

Kevin Williams

Ergonomist

January 2014 – August 2014

Ooshew, Vancouver, BC, Canada

- **Job Demands Analyses:** Conducted for all current position and created a comprehensive method and chart for Job Demands Analyses to be conducted in the future.
- **Educational Material:** Created a number of brochures to illustrate common office ergonomic concerns and musculoskeletal disorders.
- **Fitness Assessment:** Assessed the fitness level of workers to create a baseline of strength, endurance and range of motion as a method to compare post-rehabilitation performance following a potential injury.

Ergonomist; Volunteer

April 2013 – August 2013

City of Vancouver, Vancouver, BC, Canada

- **Return to Work:** Helped improve workstations for injured workers placed in modified duties during return to work programs.
- **Ergonomic Consultation:** Met with a number of stakeholders on issues such as computer use within vehicles, iPad carrying devices and parking meter collection.

Office Assistant & Press Operator

2006 - 2009

Presto Print Ltd., Richmond, BC, Canada

- Data Entry: Managed a database of sale records and intake of new print orders.
- **Customer Service:** Responded to customer inquiries conscientiously and with success in getting their needs met.

INTERESTS

- Playing all manner of games. Currently spending most of my gaming time on turn based tactics games and Magic the Gathering.
- Audiobooks and podcasts for the commute. Brandon Sanderson is my favorite author, with the Debug Log and many others for development news.
- Competed in many tennis, soccer and track and field leagues.

References Available Upon Request